Guide to the Stuart Stein papers, [ca. 1960-1995]
Stein, Stuart papers, [ca. 1960-1995]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Stuart Stein papers, [ca. 1960-1995]
15-02-3442
Stuart W. Stein
15.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, financial records, meeting minutes and agenda, class notes, and student work.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers, including correspondence, photographs, financial records, meeting minutes and agenda, class notes, and student work, relating to Stuart W. Stein's professional career as a consultant for planning, urban renewal, housing and urban design, land use planning, and historic preservation planning, as well as, his professorship in the Department of City and Regional Planning at Cornell University.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Stuart W. Stein graduated with a Bachelor in Architecture in 1952 and a Master in City Planning in 1954 from Massachusettes Institute of Technology. He served as the principle planner for the Rhode Island Development Council from 1954-1957. In 1957, he became a partner in Blair and Stein Associates, a planning consulting firm in Providence, R.I., Washington, D.C., and Syracuse, N.Y., where he worked until 1962. He taught in the Department of City and Regional Planning at Cornell University from 1962-; served as acting Chairman of the Department between 1969-1970; was Chairman of the Department from 1971-1975; and also served as the Associate Dean of the College of Architecture, Art & Planning at Cornell University from 1970-1971.
Also, Stuart W. Stein was involved in public service, including membership in the New York State Board of Historic Preservation, the Committee on National Register Nominations, and the Review Panel for the New York State Council on the Arts, Architecture and Environmental Arts Division. He served on a number of Tompkins County, New York boards, including a term as Chairman of the Ithaca Planning and Development Board, member of the county Transportation Board, member of the Ithaca City Council, and member of the Ithaca Board of Public Works. In addition, he worked professionally as an urban planning consulting and visiting professor and lecturer at the University of Puerto Rico and the University of Rhode Island. He was involved in a number of professional organizations, including the American Institute of Planners (AIP), Interamerican Planning Society, and the American Society of Planning Officials (ASPO).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Papers, including correspondence, photographs, financial records, meeting minutes and agenda, class notes, and student work, relating to Stuart W. Stein's professional career as a consultant for planning, urban renewal, housing and urban design, land use planning, and historic preservation planning, as well as, his professorship in the Department of City and Regional Planning at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Stein, Stuart W.; Werbizky, Tatiana G.; Reps, John W.; Czamanski, Stanislaw; Cornell University. College of Architecture, Art, and Planning.; Cornell University. College of Architecture, Art, and Planning. Dept. of City and Regional Planning.; American Society of Planning Officials.; New York (State). Office of Parks, Recreation, and Historic Preservation.; New York (State). Office of Parks, Recreation, and Historic Preservation. State Board for Historic Preservation.
Subjects:
City planning.; Regional planning.; City planning--Study and teaching.; Regional planning--Study and teaching.; City planning--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Regional planning--New York (State)--Tompkins County.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs; Maps
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Boxes:
Series II. Cornell University
Boxes
Series III. College of Architecture, Art and Planning
Boxes
Series IV. Professional Consulting
Boxes:
Series V. Professional Activity
Boxes:
Series VI. New York State Office of Parks, Recreation, and Historic Preservation
Boxes:
Series VII. Community Activity & Service
Boxes
Series VIII. Miscellany
Boxes
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, January-August 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, September 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January-August 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, March 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, April-December 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, January-May 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, June-December 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Low Priority Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence re: Clarence Stein (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence re: Core Curricula, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - re: New York State Legislation (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Boyar, V. Wesley, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence to/from Tania Werbizky, 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Series II. Cornell University
  - Miscellaneous
    - Cornell and its Community, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Cornell Indicators, April 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Centre for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Centre for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy I. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Centre for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy II. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Centre for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy III. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Centre for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy IV. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Center for Urban Development Research (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Center for Urban Development Research: "Mobilizing Technical Planning Services for Community Groups." (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Clarence Stein Institute (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Conference - Economic Impact of the Arts, May 27-28, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Conference of the Humanistic Aspects of the Problems of the City (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Faculty Travel: Travel and Hotel Information (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Fine Arts Library: Selected Acquisitions, December 1971 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Hammerman Gaming, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Institute on Responsiveness to Community Needs (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station: Parrott Hall (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - New York State College of Human Ecology: Human Services Training Project (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - New York State College of Human Ecology: Field Study Office (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Human Services Program - Field Study (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Resource Information Laboratory (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Committees
    - African Center Liason Committee (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Campus Planning Committe I., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Campus Planning Committe II., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - CaRDI: Community and Rural Development Institute I. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - CaRDI: Community and Rural Development Institute II. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - CaRDI: [W.K.] Kellogg [Foundation] - Local Govt. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Commencement Committee, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Commencement Committe I., 1989 & 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Commencement Committe II., 1989 & 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Commencement Committe III., 1989 & 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives, December 15, 1970- April 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives, May-October 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives, November-December 1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives, January-April 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives, May-December 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives: Executive Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives: Research Policies Committee I. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives: Research Policies Committee II. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Council of Representatives: Research Policies Committee III. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Papers, Reports & Publications
    - "Design for Living: The Resident's View of Multi-Family Housing" - Summary of Final Report to New York State Urban Development Corp. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Report to the President by Dean Kelly Burnham, July 30, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - An Application of Sequential Air Photo Analysis to the Identification and Mapping of Closed Landfill Sites, by Eugenia M. Barnaba & Arlynn W. Ingram (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - The Design of Natural Resources Inventories by Ernest E. Hardy (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Academic Integrity Handbook, September 1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Newsletter, Spring 1980, Fall 1981 & Spring/Summer 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Cornell Daily Sun (photocopy), May 6, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Cornell University Calendar, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Cornell University Map, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Cornell University: Miscellaneous Publications (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Sponsored Programs Newsletter, July 24, 1987, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Tools for Leadership: Building Cultural Partnerships (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - New York State College of Agriculture Publication re: Soil Surveys (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Programs & Program Proposals
    - Proposal by Dean of Graduate School, W.D. Cooke, September 1968 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Ethnic-Puerto Rican Studies Proposal (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Ethnic-Puerto Rican Studies Proposal (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Housing Assistance Program I. (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Housing Assistance Program II. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Lilly Endowment Proposal, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Park and Research Institute (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Save Cornell's Ag. Quad (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Student Support Services (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Transportation Program Proposal (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Transportation Program Proposal I. (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Transportation Program Proposal II. (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - University Research: Policies and Procedures for Sponsored Projects (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Series III. College of Architecture, Art & Planning
  - General
    - Architecture, Art & Planning Newsletter, 1983-Spring 1985 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - History Courses: Student Assessment (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Degrees Conferred, 1876-1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Code of Academic Integrity for Undergraduate Students (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Operational Procedures (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - College Committees & Meetings
    - College Council Meetings, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - College Council Meeting, New York City, February 2-3, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - College Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - College Meetings, 1971-1972 & December 4, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Academic Integrity Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Academic Policy Committee, 1972, 1974 & n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - College Space Committee: Sibley Space Needs, February-March 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - College Space Committee, November-December 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Dean's Search Committee, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - New College Committee (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Quality Circle: Minutes, April 29, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Newark Urban Institute Program, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Research Programs (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Architecture Department
    - History of Architecture Program (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Field of History of Architecture & Urban Development (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Field of History of Architecture and Urban Development (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Field of History of Architecture and Urban Development: Faculty, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Architecture Faculty, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Thomas Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Architecture Department Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Architecture 545: Design and Conservation - Course Outline, Fall 1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Accredited Schools of Architecture, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Landscape Architecture
    - Landscape Architecture Program: Internship Program Proposal, Interim Report (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Hughsonville and Red Hood, New York Project (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 42nd Street Prospects for Redevelopment (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Real Estate
    - Real Estate Field (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Department of City and Regional Planning
    - Admissions & Enrollment
      - Admissions, Spring 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Admissions: General Material (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Blank Transcript Card (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Application/Admission Data, 1963-67 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Admission/Application Evaluation, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Admission/Application Evaluation, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - 1968-69 Admissions I., February-March 1968 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - 1968-69 Admissions II., February-March 1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - [Course Enrollment] - Students, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Course Enrollment, Fall 1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Department Enrollment Trends/Class Size/Space Needs (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Graduate School - Quotas (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - PH.D. Transfers, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Admissions (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Admissions Information (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Miscellaneous Information from Central Admissions/College Admissions (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Admissions Correspondence, Fall 1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Undergrad Inquiries, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Admissions Inquiries, to 1981 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Admissions Inquiries, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Undergraduate Program in Urban and Regional Studies: Admissions Inquiries, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Alumni
      - Alumni (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Alumni List, April 15, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Alumni Files - Rochereau (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Committees & Meetings
      - Faculty Meeting, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Convention Materials, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Cranch Committee Report, October 1972-February 1973 & n.d. (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Interdepartmental Committee, November-December 1971 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - Thesis Committees (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Curriculum
      - Program Information
        - Department of City and Regional Planning, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 56)
        - Area Requirments/Curriculum, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 57)
        - Career Office - Job Notifications (Box 3, Folder 58)
        - Department Notes (Box 3, Folder 59)
        - Urban Planning and Development and Policy Planning & Regional Analysis Department Merger, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 60)
        - CRP 50th Anniversary (Box 3, Folder 61)
        - Graduate School (Box 3, Folder 62)
        - CRP Internship Policy (Box 3, Folder 63)
        - Law - Planning Joint Program (Box 3, Folder 64)
        - MLA - MRP Joint Program, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 65)
        - MRP Thesis Policies and Procedures (Box 3, Folder 66)
        - Preliminary Site Visit Report, Submitted to the Planning Accreditationn Board, March 6, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 67)
        - Program Publicity (Box 3, Folder 68)
        - Treaty between the Department of Urban Planning & Development and the Department of Policy Planning & Regional Analysis, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 69)
        - Treaty between the Graduate School and the Filed of City and Regional Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 70)
        - Urban Planning & Development: General Information, September 1971 (Box 3, Folder 71)
        - Urban Planning & Development: General Program Statement (Box 3, Folder 72)
        - Urban Planning & Development, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 73)
        - Urban Planning & Development: Quality Report, Evaluation Criteria, Basic Concepts & Definitions (Box 3, Folder 74)
        - Urban Planning & Development: Start-Up Material Beginning of Academic Year (Box 3, Folder 75)
        - Urban & Regional Studies - Graduate Field (Box 3, Folder 76)
        - Urban & Regional Studies: Urban Studies Program Leading to Bachelor's Degree (Box 3, Folder 77)
        - Urban & Regional Studies (Box 3, Folder 78)
        - Urban & Regional Studies: Undergraduate Urban & Regional Planning I. (Box 3, Folder 79)
        - Urban & Regional Studies: Undergraduate Urban & Regional Planning II. (Box 3, Folder 80)
        - Urban & Regional Studies: Undergraduate Brochures (Box 3, Folder 81)
        - Urban & Regional Studies: Undergraduate Brochures - Originals (Box 3, Folder 82)
        - Albany Summer Internship (Box 3, Folder 83)
        - Summer Session, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 84)
        - History [of Planning] Course- Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 85)
      - Course Materials
        - UPD 349: Course Reserve Request Form (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - CRP 432: Transportation: It's Urban Impact (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - UPD 524: Transportation and the Urban Environment - Course Outline (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - CRP 552: Urban Land Use Planning I. (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - CRP 552: Urban Land Use Planning I. (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - CRP 552: Urban Land Use Planning I. - Student Exercises - Copies of Good Examples, Spring 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        - CRP 552: Urban Land Use Planning I. - Student Work, Spring 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - CRP 552: Urban Land Use Planning I. - Student Work, Spring 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - CRP 552: Urban Land Use Planning I. - Student Work, Spring 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - CRP 552: Intro. to Government Programs for Urban Renewal (Box 4, Folder 10)
        - CRP 552: Intro. to Government Programs in Urban Renewal - "Home Steading in the 70's" by Faneen M. Murray (Box 4, Folder 11)
        - CRP 553: Urban Land Use Planning II. (Box 4, Folder 12)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Course Work Typing - Stein (Box 4, Folder 13)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Handout - Identification of Architectural Styles, Spring 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Handout - Impressions of Collegetown, A Sensory Awareness Exercise, September 1981 & 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Student Work, Fall 1980 & 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Student Work, Fall 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Student Work, Fall 1983 & n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design, Fall 1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Student Maps, Spring 1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Student Maps, to get home (Box 4, Folder 21)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Maps, Fall 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Ithaca Maps (Box 4, Folder 23)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Neighborhood Maps, Fall 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Student Maps, Home/Sibley, Fall 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Diagnostic Exams - Completed, Fall 1977 (Box 4, Folder 26)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Diagnostic Exams - Completed, Fall 1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Diagnostic Exams - Completed & Exam Drafts, Fall 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Diagnostic Exams & Image Maps, Fall 1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - NY Diagnostic Exams - Completed, Fall 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
        - CRP 554: Introduction to Planning Design - Student Diagnostic Exams, Fall 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop (Box 4, Folder 32)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop (from binder), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop (from binder), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop (from binder), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Articles (Box 4, Folder 37)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET [Built Environment Education Team] (Box 4, Folder 38)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET, Spring 1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Handout Packet (Box 4, Folder 40)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Lesson Plans/Samples (Box 4, Folder 41)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 42)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Miscellaneous to be sorted I. (Box 4, Folder 43)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Miscellaneous to be sorted II. (Box 4, Folder 44)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Miscellaneous to be sorted III. (Box 4, Folder 45)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - NEA Contract, Budget & Grant Materials, Granted $6,100, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - NEA Proposal, Not Granted, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Teacher Evaluation Forms, Spring 1983 (Box 4, Folder 48)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - BEET - Video Proposal - Ziegler (Box 4, Folder 49)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Built Environment Education Center, Philadelphia, P.A. (Box 4, Folder 50)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Certificates (Box 4, Folder 51)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Donovan Academy (Box 4, Folder 52)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Handouts (from binder) (Box 4, Folder 53)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - History Slides (Box 4, Folder 54)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Information and Resources (Box 4, Folder 55)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Journal Table of Contents, Belle Sherman Elementary School, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 56)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Journal of Glen C. Dake, Dryden Elementary, May 19, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 57)